

7599850002

www.calloftheforest.com

My Mission

As a yoga teacher I share the traditional teachings of Hatha yoga, incorporating asanas, pranayama and meditation. I provide students clear alignment instructions, confirming hands on adjustments and pointings towards meditative awareness. Together we create a loving, open space, where all are welcome to explore and experience the natural state.

Education and Certification

RYT 200 March 2017 Hatha Yoga World, Rishikesh, India BSC (Hons) Multimedia Technology First Class 2003-2005 Nottingham Trent University

Workshops and Retreats

2 Day Somatic Meditation Workshop July 2015 Dharma Ocean, London, England

5 Day Metta Retreat October 2015 Amaravati, Hertfordshire England

14 Day Gurgief Movements Workshop March 2016 Osho Nisarga ,Dharamsala India

12 Day Iyengar Yoga IntensiveApril 2016Himalayan Yoga Centre ,Dharamsala India

10 Day Self Inquiry Retreat with Mooji September 2016 Monte Sahaja, Portugal

10 Day Vipassana Meditation Retreat December 2016 Dharma Dipu, Herefordshire, England

Teaching Experience

Yoga Teacher April 2017 Aliens Camp, Afrika Burn, South Africa

Private Yoga Teacher April 2017 – Present

Other Work Experience

Frontend Developer 2013 – 2015 BBC Worldwide, London

